logaster.com 2019-01-08

# Privacy Policy | Logaster - Online Logo Generator

﻿Last updated September 5, 2018

 **Privacy Policy**

G-Score Technologies Ltd, d.b.a. “Logaster” (“we”, “our”, or “Logaster”), is committed to protecting the privacy of its users and we therefore ask that you (“you”, “your” or the “User”) please read this Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) before providing us with any information about you or any other person.

This Privacy Policy describes how we collect and use the Personal data you provide throughout our website at [https://logaster.com ](https://logaster.com/)(the “Website”), the options, choices and rights you have in connection with the Personal data we collect.

 **Personal data and information we collect**

Any information relating to you as a specific person, which can be used to identify you, directly or indirectly, including information about your activities when directly linked to personally identifiable information, is deemed to be your personal information (the “Personal data”).

When you access or use the Website, Logaster may collect a series of Personal data and other information about you. The types of information we collect may include your name, email address, postal address, phone number, social networks information and other information you choose to provide. Also, we automatically collect such information about your use of the Website:

  * the browser types and versions used,

  * the operating system used by your device,

  * the date and time of access to the Website,

  * your location an Internet protocol address (IP address),

  * any other similar data and information that may be used in the event of attacks on our information technology systems.

Logaster also processes anonymous data, aggregated or not, to analyze and produce statistics related to the habits, usage patterns, and demographics of users as a group or as individuals. Such anonymous data does not allow to identify you or other individual and we may share anonymous data, aggregated or not, with third parties.

 **How we use Personal data and information**

We use data and information that we collect to:

  * provide our products and services, including this Website, and improve them over time, 
  * deliver the content of our Website correctly, 

  * optimize the content of our Website, as well as its advertisement, 

  * personalize and manage our relationship with you, including introducing you to products or services that may be of interest to you, 

  * provide customer support,

  * comply with the applicable laws and regulations,

  * investigate, respond to, and manage inquiries or events, 

  * to conduct research, including for public interest and scientific purposes,

  * provide law enforcement authorities with the information necessary for criminal prosecution in case of a cyber-attack. 

We may analyze anonymously collected data and information statistically, with the aim of increasing the data protection and data security of our enterprise, and to ensure an optimal level of protection for the Personal data we process. The anonymous data of the server log files are stored separately from all Personal data provided by you.

While using your Personal data Logaster does not draw any conclusions about you. We may analyze your personal information to create a profile of your interests and preferences so that we can contact you with information relevant to you. We may make use of additional information about you when it is available from external sources to help us do this effectively.

 **How we share your Personal data**

We may share your Personal data with your consent or as necessary to complete any transaction or provide any service or product you have ordered or requested. For example, we may share your email address with our partner, who manages the dispatch of emails for Logaster.

Sometimes and in certain situations Logaster may share your Personal data with:

  * SendGrid, Inc., The Rocket Science Group LLC, Zendesk, Inc. for the purposes of processing emails;

  * Paymentwall Inc., BlueSnap, Inc., PayPal, Inc. and our banking partners for the purposes of processing payments;

  * law enforcement, government officials, or other third parties when we are compelled to do so by a subpoena, court order, or similar legal procedure; or we believe in good faith that the disclosure of Personal data is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss, to report suspected illegal activity or to investigate violations of any of our policies;
  * our Personal data processing counterparties or agents, third party identification service providers hired by or cooperating with us, whose services are required by us from the practical point of view;
  * individuals, who are our exclusive contractors;

  * other third parties only with your prior consent or direction to do so.

We will not provide your Personal data to any other website users without your consent or direction.

Our services may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers, and affiliates (including, but not limited to, websites on which the Website is advertised). If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites and any services that may be accessible through them have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies or for any Personal data that may be collected through these websites or services, such as contact and location data. Please check these policies before you submit any Personal data to these websites or use these services.

 **Retention of Personal data**

Logaster processes and stores your Personal data only for the period necessary to achieve the purpose of storage. Nevertheless, we may retain certain Personal data or information for legitimate business purposes or as required by the law. In case we retain your Personal data for any legitimate business purpose other than to provide our services, we will make efforts to limit the access to the Personal data and the retention time to minimum.

If the storage purpose is not applicable, or if a storage period prescribed by law expires, the Personal data are routinely blocked or erased in accordance with legal requirements.

 **Your rights as to the Personal data we collect**

You have certain rights and protections under the applicable laws regarding the processing of your Personal data:

  * You have the right to obtain from us the confirmation as to whether or not Personal data concerning you are being processed. 

  * You have the right to obtain from us free information about your Personal data stored at any time and a copy of this information (including the purpose of processing, categories of Personal data concerned, storage period, and more).

  * You have the right to obtain from us without undue delay the rectification of inaccurate Personal data concerning you. Taking into account the purposes of the processing, you have the right to have incomplete Personal data completed, including by means of providing a supplementary statement. 

  * You have the right to withdraw your consent for collection of Personal data provided hereunder, and obtain from us the erasure of Personal data concerning you with undue delay, and we have the obligation to erase Personal data without undue delay, as long as the processing is no longer necessary. 

  * You have the right to obtain from us restriction of processing if the processing is unlawful, if you contest the accuracy of your Personal data or your Personal data is no longer needed by the Company.
  * You have the right to receive from us the Personal data concerning you, in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format. 

  * You can ask to transfer your Personal data in accordance with your right to data portability to a third party.
  * You have the right not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing, including profiling, which produces legal effects concerning you or similarly significantly affecting you.

You can exercise your choice by contacting us at: [support@logaster.com](mailto:support@logaster.com), or through other means and solutions provided by Logaster.

Please note that when you send us a request to exercise your rights, we may need to reasonably authenticate your identity. Thus, Logaster may ask you to provide credentials to make sure that you are who you claim to be and will further ask you certain questions to understand the nature and scope of your request.

 **Cookies**

Our Website uses cookies. When you access the Website we, or third parties on our behalf (e.g. Google Analytics, Yandex.Metrica or similar service providers) may place small data files called ‘cookies’ on your computer or other device. We use these technologies to recognize you as our user; customize our Website and advertising; measure promotional effectiveness and collect information about your computer or other access device to mitigate risk, help prevent fraud, and promote trust and safety.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies but provide controls that allow you to block or delete them. Please refer to your browser's privacy or help documentation to find instructions for blocking or deleting cookies. However, please note that certain features of Logaster services and products depend on cookies, and if you choose to block cookies, you may be unable to sign in or use some of those services, features, and preferences that are dependent on cookies will be lost. If you choose to delete cookies, settings and preferences controlled by those cookies, including advertising preferences, are deleted and will need to be recreated.

 **Transfer of Personal data outside your territory**

Personal data collected by Logaster may be stored, transferred and processed in your region, in the U.S., European Economic Area and Ukraine. If you are a resident in a jurisdiction where transfer of your Personal data to another jurisdiction requires your consent, then you hereby provide us with your freely given, specific, informed, and unambiguous consent to such transfer to the above jurisdictions.

In case we collect or store your Personal data in the European Economic Area, we may also transfer Personal data to other countries, some of which have not yet been determined by the European Commission to have an adequate level of data protection, and when we do so, we use a variety of legal mechanisms, including contracts, to help ensure your rights and protections are transferred together with your data. Logaster complies with the Privacy Shield Framework when your Personal data is transferred from EU or Switzerland to the U.S.

 **Security**

Logaster takes commercially reasonable measures and relevant technologies to help protect information about you from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. For example, we limit the access to the Personal data stored, use encryption, when necessary etc.

 **Changes in this policy**

We may make changes to this Policy from time to time, and where we do so, we change the ‘Last updated’ date of this Policy above. If there is a material change to this Policy, such as a change to the purposes of Processing of Personal data that is not consistent with the purpose for which it was originally collected, Logaster will notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes before they take effect or by directly sending you a notification.

We encourage you to review the Policy whenever you access or use our Website to stay informed about our information practices and the choices available to you. If you do not agree to the revised Policy, you should discontinue your use of this Website.

 **Applicable law and arbitration**

This Policy, where possible, shall be governed by the laws of the country of Logaster’s location. Unless otherwise expressly directed by the applicable laws, any claims, disputes or controversies related to this Policy shall be finally settled by the authorized court at Logaster’s place of residence.

 **Contact Us**

We welcome your feedback. If you have any comments or concerns about this Policy or would like to contact us for any reason, you may reach Logaster at the following address: [support@logaster.com](mailto:support@logaster.com)

* * *

In cases of variation, the English version shall prevail.
